Guide to the Stanford University, Commission of Engineers, Records
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographs
  - Prints (cyanotypes and black/white) from numbered series
    - Arcades, physics bldg. to small physics bldg. west wall [Negative# 19-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Hist. & eng. bldg. - s.w. elevation [Negative# 20-1 ] (Box 12)
    - Memorial Arch - view from front [Negative# 20-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Surface drainage - mech. eng. lab [Negative# 20-8 ] (Box 12)
    - Assembly Hall - w. rear exit stairway [Negative# 21-1 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building - rear center [Negative# 21-6 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building - rear center [Negative# 21-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Chemistry building - interior wall (2 cc.) [Negative# 22-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Repairing arcades [Negative# 25-1 ] (Box 12)
    - Wall between Quad and engineering labs [Negative# 25-2 ] (Box 12)
    - Wall between Quad and engineering labs [Negative# 25-3 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade, Geology corner [Negative# 25-4 ] (Box 12)
    - Interior roof support damage [Negative# 25-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Interior roof support damage [Negative# 25-6 ] (Box 12)
    - Building interior [Negative# 25-7 ] (Box 12)
    - Interior wall damage [Negative# 25-8 ] (Box 12)
    - Interior wall damage [Negative# 25-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade (2 cc.) [Negative# 26-5 ] (Box 12)
    - Engineering labs (2 cc.) [Negative# 26-9 ] (Box 12)
    - Quad corner [Negative# 26-10 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade by rear of Church (2 cc.) [Negative# 26-12 ] (Box 12)
    - Arcade roof (number missing) (Box 12)
    - Arcade repair (number missing) (Box 12)
  - Contact prints for number series 1 through 3 (Box 13)
  - Contact prints for number series 8 through 10 (Box 13)
  - Contact prints for number series 11 through 13 (Box 13)
  - Contact prints for number series 14 through 16 (Box 13)
  - Photographs to accompany the Report of the Commission of Engineers to the Board of Trustees, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Records
  - Work to be done (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Daily journal of the Earthquake Commission (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Estimates for the cost of repairing the buildings (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Estimates for the cost of subdividing and improving tracts (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Progress reports made to the Board of Trustees, [Folder 5 or 6 includes copy of the June 1906 Report on Condition of Buildings...], 1906 Jul - 1908 Dec (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Progress reports made to the Board of Trustees, 1906 Jul - 1908 Dec (Box 5, Folder 6)